Finding Aid for Jeffrey R. Parsons papers, 1960-2013
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Archaeological Sites and Projects 1966-2010
  - Texcoco 1967
    - Site Reports
      - Tx-F-10 (II) San Joaquin (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-11 (II) (MF) (Box 12)
      - Tx-F-12 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-C-1 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-C-2 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-C-3 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-C-4 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-C-5 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-C-6 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-C-7 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-C-8 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-C-9 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-C-10 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-C-11 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-T-1 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-T-2 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-T-3 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-T-4 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-T-5 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-T-6 (IIb) Tx-A-1 (II) (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-2 (II) Tx-LA-45 (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-3 (II) Tx-LA-45 (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-4 (II) Tx-LA-52 (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-5 (II) Tx-LA-51 (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-6 (II) Tx-LA-50 (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-7 (II) Tx-LA-54 (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-8 (II) Tx-La-55 (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-9 (II) Tx-LA-53 (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-10 (II) Tx-LA-87 [Huexotla] (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-11 (II) Tx-LA-56 [Texcoco] (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-12 (II) Tx-LA-87 Coatlinchan Frontier (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-13 (II) Tx-LA-64 (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-14 (II) Tx-LA-65 (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-15 (II) Tx-LA-66 (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-16 (II) Tx-LA-61 (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-17 (II) Tx-LA-57 (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-18 (II) Tx-LA-64 (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-19 (IIc) Tx-LA-87 (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-20 (IIc) Tx-LA-86 (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-21 (IIc) Tx-LA-60 (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-22 (IIc) Tx-LA-59 (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-23 (IIc) Tx-LA-58 (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-24 (IIc) Tx-LA-80 (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-25 (IIc) Tx-LA-80 (Box 12)
      - Tx-A-26 (IIc) Tx-LA-85 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-27 (IIc) Tx-LA-84 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-28 (IIc) Tx-LA-79 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-29 (IIc) Tx-LA-61 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-30 (IIc) Tx-LA-82 Aqueduct A and Vicinity (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-31 (II) Tx-LA-62 Tetzcotzingo Baths (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-32 (II) Tx-LA-76 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-33 (II) E. half-Tx-LA-72 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-34 (II) Tx-LA-78 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-35 (II) Tx-LA-77 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-36 (II) Tx-LA-81 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-37 (II) Tx-LA-72 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-38 (II) Tx-LA-75 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-39 (II) Tx-LA-69 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-40 (II) Tx-LA-70 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-41 (II) Tx-LA-72 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-42 (II) Tx-La-72 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-43 (II) Tx-LA-71 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-44 (II) Tx-LA-63 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-45 (II) Cerro Tlaloc Aztec Ceremonial Site (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-46 (II) Tx-LA-72 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-47 (II) Tx-LA-72 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-48 (II) Tx-LA-72 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-49 (II) Tx-LA-73 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-50 (II) Tx-LA-72 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-51 (IIa) Tx-LA-47 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-52 (IIa) Tx-LA-49 (west half) Tx-LA-56 (east half) (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-53 (IIa) Tx-LA-48 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-54 (IIb) Tx-LA-42 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-55 (IIb) Tx-LA-43 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-56 (II) Tx-LA-67 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-57 (II)Aztec water canal above Purificación (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-58 (II) Tx-LA-68 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-1 (III) Tx-A-110 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-2 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-3 (III) Tx-A-109 "Aztec Chimalhuacan" (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-4 (III) Tx-A-108 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-5 (III) Tx-A-5 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-6 (III) Tx-A-107 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-7 (III) Tx-A-106 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-8 (III) Tx-A-105 Aztec component at Temesco (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-9 (III) Tx-A-101 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-10 (III) Tx-A-100 (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-11 (III) Tx-A-99 Aztec Coatepec (Box 13)
      - Tx-A-12 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-C-1 (III) "Classic Chimalhuacan" (Box 13)
      - Tx-C-2 (III) Portezuela Classic (Box 13)
      - Tx-C-3 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-C-4 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-C-5 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-C-6 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-C-7 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-C-8 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-T-1 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-T-2 (III) "Toltecc Chimalhuacan" (Box 13)
      - Tx-T-3 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-T-4 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-T-5 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-T-6 (III) Portezuela Toltec (Box 13)
      - Tx-T-7 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-T-8 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-T-9 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-T-10 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-F-1 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-F-2 (III) Tx-TF-46 "El Tepalcate" (Box 13)
      - Tx-F-3 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-F-4 (III) (Also Early Classic Material) (Box 13)
      - Tx-F-5 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-F-6 (III) "Temesco" (Box 13)
      - Tx-F-7 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-F-8 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-F-9 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-F-10 (III) (Box 13)
      - Tx-F-11 (III) (Box 13)
      - Ix-Coyo-2 Tx-ET-17 (Box 13)
      - Strip II-Survey to be completed (Box 13)
      - Ceramic Data 1967 (Box 13)
      - Tx-Q-1 (III) (Box 13)
    - Field Notebooks
      - Texcoco Survey Strip I Books 1 and 2 1967 (Box 13)
      - Texcoco Survey Strip I Books 3 and 4 1967 (Box 13)
      - Texcoco Survey Strip IIc and Strip II Book I 1967 (Box 13)
      - Texcoco Survey Strip II Books 2 and 3 1967 (Box 13)
      - Texcoco Survey Strip III Books 1,2 and 3 1967 (Box 13)
      - Texcoco Survey Finances 1967 (Box 13)
      - Personal Photo Record 1967 (Box 13)
      - Readings from Chapingo Metro Station 1962-1966 (Box 13)
  - Chalco 1969
    The Chalco 1969 sub series (1.25 linear feet) is made up of the survey site reports, ceramic analysis files, and site notebooks. Data was gathered by Parsons' team including Mary Hrones Parsons, Michael Baylis, Bruce Jaffee, and Parsons.
    - Site Reports
      - Miscellaneous Photos-Summer 1966 (Box 14)
      - Sherd Counts, Type Collection and Site Keys 1969 (Box 14)
      - Chalco Region Survey-Classic Sites 1969 (Box 14)
      - Chalco Region Survey-Aztec Sites 1969 (Box 14)
      - Chalco Region Survey-Late Toltec Sites 1969 (Box 14)
      - Chalco Region Survey-Early Toltec Sites 1969 (Box 14)
      - Chalco Region Survey-Formative Sites 1969 (Box 14)
      - Chalco Region Survey-Site Area Measurements 1969 (Box 14)
      - Chalco 1969 Survey-Miscellaneous Photos, 1969 (Box 14)
      - Teotihuacan Valley 1966 (Box 14)
      - Chalco-Original Ceramic Analysis 1969 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-1-east side of Xico island (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-2 Ch-ET-2 Ch-Az-24 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-3 Ch-ET-3 Ch-Az-25 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-4 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-5 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-6 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-7 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-8 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-9 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-10 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-11 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-12 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-13 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-14 Ch-Az-33 Ch-ET-5 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-15 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-17 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-18 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-19 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-20 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-21 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-22 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-23 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-24 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-25 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-26 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-27 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-29 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-30 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-31 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-32 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-33 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-34 Ch-ET (Box 14)
      - Ch-Az-35. (Box 14)
      - Ch-Az-36 (Box 14)
      - Ch-Az-37 (Box 14)
      - Ch-Az-39 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-41 (Box 14)
      - Ch-A-42 (Box 14)
      - Ch-Az-43 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-1 Ch-ET-1 Ch-LT-13 Xico island (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-2 Ch-ET-2 Ch-A2-25 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-3 Ch-A2-33 Ch-ET-5 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-4 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-5 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-6 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-7 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-8 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-9 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-11 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-12 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-13 Ch-LT-5 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-14 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-15 Ch-LT-1 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-16 Ch-LT-2 Ch-A2-3 Ch-ET- (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-17 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-18 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-19 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-20 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-21 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-22 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-23 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-24 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-25 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-26 Ch-ET- (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-27 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-28 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-29 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-30 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-31 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-32 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-33 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-34 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-35 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-36 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-37 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-38 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-39 (Box 14)
      - Ch-T-40 (Box 14)
      - Ch-C-1 (Box 14)
      - Ch-C-2 Ch-Cl-9 (Box 14)
      - Ch-C-3 Ch-Cl-4 (Box 14)
      - Ch-C-4 Ch-Cl-5 (Box 14)
      - Ch-C-5 Ch-Cl-10 (Box 14)
      - Ch-C-6 Ch-Cl-15 (Box 14)
      - Ch-C-7 Ch-Cl-12 Ch-TF-25 (Box 14)
      - Ch-C-8 Ch-Cl-13 (Box 14)
      - Ch-C-9 Ch-Cl-14 (Box 14)
      - Ch-C-10 Ch-Cl-3 (Box 14)
      - Ch-C-11 Ch-Cl-2 (Box 14)
      - Ch-C-12 Ch-Cl-1 (Box 14)
      - Ch-C-13 (Box 14)
      - Ch-C-14 (Box 14)
      - Ch-C-15 Ch-Cl-16 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-1 Ch-LT-13 Ch-LF-5 CH-TF-9 CH-Cl-8 Ch-ET-1 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-2 Ch-MF-6 Ch-LF-6 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-3 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-4 Ch-MF-5 Ch-LF-4 Ch-Cl-6 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-5 Ch-TF-36 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-6 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-7 Ch-TF-14 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-8 Ch-TF-12 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-9 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-10 Ch-MF-4 Ch-LF-3 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-11 Ch-TF-25 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-12 Ch-TF-23 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-13 Ch-MF-7 Ch-LF-7 Ch-TF-26 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-14 Ch-TF-15 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-15 Ch-MF-3 Ch-LF-2 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-16 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-17 Ch-MF-2 Ch-Az-2 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-18 Ch-MF-1 Ch-Az-1 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-19 Ch-ET- (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-20 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-21 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-22 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-23 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-24 Ch-TF-27 Ch-TF-28 Ch-MF-8 Ch-MF-9 Ch-LF-8 Ch-LF-9 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-25 Ch-TF-22 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-26 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-27 Ch-TF-19 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-28 Ch-LF-15 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-29 Ch-LF-16 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-31 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-32 Ch-LF-144 Ch-TF-31 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-33 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-34 Ch-LF-10 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-35 (Box 14)
      - Ch-F-36 (Box 14)
      - Type, Location and Sites (Box 14)
    - Field Notebooks (Box 15)
      - Book 1 & 2 (Box 15)
      - Ceramic profiles (Box 15)
  - Ixtapalapa 1969
    The Ixtapalapa 1969 sub series (2 linear feet) contains the survey site reports, site notebooks, sherd profile cards, site photos, and a card file that illustrates the correspondence between field numbers and final site numbers. Data in the site notebooks was gathered by Richard Blanton, and Doug White.
    - Site Reports
      - Ixtapalapa site folders with ceramic analysis sheets (Box 15)
      - Ix-F-1 (Box 15)
      - LF-1 (Box 15)
      - Ix-F-7, EF-1, MF-1 (Box 15)
      - Ix-EF-3 (Box 15)
      - Ix-MF-4 (Box 15)
      - Ix-LF-2 TF-4 (Box 15)
      - Ix-LF-3 (Box 15)
      - Ix-LF-4 (Box 15)
      - Ix-EF-2 MF-2 LF-5 (Box 15)
      - Ix-LF-6 (Box 15)
      - Ix-LF-7 (Box 15)
      - Ix-LF-8 (Box 15)
      - Ix-LF-9 (Box 15)
      - Ix-LF-10 (Box 15)
      - Ix-LF-11 (Box 15)
      - Ix-LF-12 (Box 15)
      - Ix-LF-13 (Box 15)
      - Ix-TF-1 (Box 15)
      - Ix-TF-2 (Box 15)
      - Ix-TF-3 (Box 15)
      - Ix-TF-5 (Box 15)
      - Ix-TF-6 (Box 15)
      - Ix-TF-7 (Box 15)
      - Ix-TF-8 (Box 15)
      - Ix-TF-9 (Box 15)
      - Ix-TF-10 (Box 15)
      - Ix-TF-11 (Box 15)
      - Ix-TF-12 (Box 15)
      - Ix-TF-13 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-1 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-2 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-3 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-4 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-5 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-6 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-7 (Box 15)
      - Formerly Ix-Az-11 See Cl-6 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-8 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-9 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-10 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-11 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-12 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-13 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-14 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-15 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-16 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-17 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-18 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-19 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-20 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-21 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-22 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-23 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-24 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-25 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-26 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-27 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-27 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-28 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-29 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-30 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-31 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-32 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-33 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-34 (23-NE-2) (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-34 (22-SE-6) (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-35 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-36 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Cl-37 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Coyo-1 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Coyo-2 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Coyo-3 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Coyo-4 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Coyo-5 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Coyo-6 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Coyo-7 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Coyo-8 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Coyo-9 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Coyo-10 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Coyo-11 (Box 15)
      - Formerly Ix-Cl-37 See Coyo-12 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Coyo-12 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Coyo-13 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Coyo-14 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Coyo-15 ET-15 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Coyo-16 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Coyo-17 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Coyo-18 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Coyo-19 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Coyo-20 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-1 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-2 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-3 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-4 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-5 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-6 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-7 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-8 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-9 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-10 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-11 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-12 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-13 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-14 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-15 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-16 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-17 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-18 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-19 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-20 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-21 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-22 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-23 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-24 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-25 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-26 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-27 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-28 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-29 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-30 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-31 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-32 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-33 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-34 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-35 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-36 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-37 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-38 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-39 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-40 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-41 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-42 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-43 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-44 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-45 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Maz-46 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Az-1 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Az-2 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Az-3 (Box 15)
      - Ix-Az-4 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-5 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-6 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-7 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-8 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-9 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-10 (Box 16)
      - Formerly Ix-Az-12 See Maz-4 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-11 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-14 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-16 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-15 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-17 (15) (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-18 (16) (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-19 (17) (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-20 (18) (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-21 (19) (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-22 (20) (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-23 (21) (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-24 (22) (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-25 (23) (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-26 A-26 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-26 (24) (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-28 Ixtapaluca Viejo II (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-27 (25) (Box 16)
      - Ix-A-27 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-29 A-26 III (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-29 (Box 16)
      - Ix-A-30 (Box 16)
      - Ix-A-31 (Box 16)
      - Ix-A-32 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-35 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-34 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-35 (Box 16)
      - Ix-A-36 (Box 16)
      - Ix-A-37 (Box 16)
      - Ix-A-38 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-39 (Box 16)
      - Ix-A-40 (Box 16)
      - Ix-A-41 (29-SW-4) (Box 16)
      - Ix-A-41 (29-SW-7) (Box 16)
      - Ix-A-42 (Box 16)
      - Ix-A-43 (Box 16)
      - Ix-A-44 (Box 16)
      - Ix-A-45 (Box 16)
      - Ix-A-46 (Box 16)
      - Ix-A-48 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-49 (Box 16)
      - Ix-A-50 (Box 16)
      - Ix-A-51 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-52 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-53 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-54 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-55 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-56 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-57 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-58 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-59 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-60 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-59 (Box 16)
      - Ix-A-61 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-62 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-63 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-64 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-65 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-66 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-67 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-68 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-69 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-70 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-71 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-72 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-73 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-74 (Box 16)
      - Ix-A-75 (Box 16)
      - Ix-Az-77 (Box 16)
      - Tl 35 Tl 34 Photo Area 173 (Box 16)
      - Sherd Profile Cards (Box 16)
    - Field Notebooks
      - Book 1 and 2 (Box 16)
      - Book 3 (Box 16)
  - Chalco-Xochimilco 1972
    The Chalco-Xochimilco 1972 subseries (4 linear feet) is composed of similar documentation for the site including reports, field notebooks, and sherd profile cards. Data for this site was gathered by Jeffrey and Mary Parsons, Robert Wenke, and Earl Prahl.
    - Site Reports
      - Mexico 1972 General Photos (Box 16)
      - Chalco-Xochimilco 1972 Spindle Whorl and Figurine Data (Box 16)
      - Mexico 1972-Photos to be mounted (Box 16)
      - Valley of Mexico Survey (Box 17)
      - Map Keys 1969, 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ceramic Analysis (Jeff) 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ceramic Analysis (Mary) 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ceramic Analysis (Wenke) 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ceramic Analysis (Prahl) 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ceramic Re-Analysis-1969 Chalco-1967 Texcoco 1972 (Box 17)
      - Valley of Mexico-Site Numbers = locations/ Features (JRP) 1972 (Box 17)
      - JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Wenke 1972 (Box 17)
      - Chalco-Xochimilco Survey 1969, 1972 (Box 17)
      - Prehispanic Occupation Tabulations (Box 17)
      - Chaco-Xochimilco Original Sherd Profiles (Box 17)
      - Chaco-Xochimilco region AZ I, Az II B/O Distribution and Chalco Polychrome (Box 17)
      - Chaco-Xochimilco Modern Population 1969, 1972 (Box 17)
      - Chaco-Xochimilco Monograph-Xerox of Appendix 2 (Box 17)
      - Miscellaneous Illustrations Chaco-Xochimilco (Box 17)
      - Miscellaneous Rough Maps (Box 17)
      - Environmental Descriptions-Valley of Mexico (for Chaco-Xochimilco monograph) (Box 17)
      - Plates used in Chaco-Xochimilco monograph (Box 17)
      - Reduced to 1:25,000-JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Middle Formative MF (JRP) 1972 (Box 17)
      - Late Formative LF (JRP) 1972 (Box 17)
      - Terminal Formative (JRP) 1972 (Box 17)
      - Classic (JRP) 1972 (Box 17)
      - Early Toltec (JRP) 1972 (Box 17)
      - Late Toltec (JRP) 1972 (Box 17)
      - Aztec (JRP) 1972 (Box 17)
      - Eastern Amecameca Valley Photos (Box 17)
      - Ch-MF-1 Chalco-West 31-A-NE JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-MF-2 Chalco-West 31-B-SE JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-MF-3 Chalco-West 40-E-North JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-MF-4 Chalco-West 40-D-NW JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LF-1 Chalco-West 31-A-NE JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LF-2 Chalco-West 40-F-North JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LF-3 Chalco-West 12-A-NE JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LF-4 Chalco-East 18-B-NW JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-TF-1 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-TF-2 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-TF-3 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-TF-4 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-TF-5 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-Cl-1 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-Cl-2 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-Cl-3 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-Cl-4 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-Cl-5 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-Cl-6 Chalco-West 12-A-NE JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-Cl-7 Chalco-West 12-C-SW JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-Cl-8 Chalco-West 12-C-SW JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-Cl-9 Chalco-West 1-C-SW JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-ET-1 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-ET-2 Chalco-West 12-A-NE 12-C-SW JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-ET-3 Chalco-West 12-C-NW JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-ET-4 Chalco-West 12-A-NW JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LT-1 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LT-2 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LT-3 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LT-4 Chalo-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LT-5 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LT-6 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LT-7 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LT-8 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LT-9 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LT-10 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LT-10 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LT-11 Chalco-West 13-D-South JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LT-12 Chalco-West 12-A-NE JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LT-13 Chalco-West 12-A-SE 12-C-SW JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LT-14 Chalco-West 12-C-NW 12-C-NW JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LT-15 Chalco-West 12-C-SW JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LT-16 Chalco-East 18-B-SW JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LT-17 Chalco-West 18-B-SW JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-LT-18 Chalco-East 18-B-SE JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-Az-1 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-Az-2 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-Az-3 Chalco-West JRP 9172 (Box 17)
      - Ch-Az-4 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-Az-5 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-Az-6 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-Az-7 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-Az-8 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-Az-9 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 17)
      - Ch-Az-10 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-11 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-12 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-13 Chalco-West JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-14 Chalco-West 32-C-NE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-15 Chalco-West 32-E-NW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-16 Chalco-West 32-F-SW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-17 Chalco-West 32-C-NW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-18 Chalco-West 32-C-NW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-19 Chalco-West 32-C-NW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-20 Chalco-West 32-C-NW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-21 Chalco-West 32-C-SW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-22 40-E-NW (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-23 Chalco-West 13-D-South JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-24 Chalco-West 13-C-NE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-25 Chalco-West 12-A-NW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-26 Chalco-West 12-A-SE (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-27 Chalco-West X-C-NE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-28 Chalco-West X-C-SE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-29 Chalco-West 31-A-NE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-30 Chalco-West 31-A-NE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-31 Chalco-West 31-A-NE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-32 Chalco-West 31-A-NE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - Ch-Az-33 Chalco-West 18-B-NW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-MF-1 Xochimilco West 52-D-NE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-LF-1 Xochimilco West 21-D-SE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-LF-2 Xochimilco West 46-B-SE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-LF-3 Xochimilco West 21-D-SE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-TF-1 Xochimilco West 21-D-SE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-TF-2 Xochimilco West 52-F-North JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-CL-1 Xochimilco West 21-D-NW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-CL-2 Xochimilco West 14-B-SW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-CL-3 Xochimilco West 14-B-NE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Cl-4 Xochimilco West 52-F-North JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Cl-5 Xochimilco West 52-F-North JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Cl-6 Xochimilco West 52-D-NE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-ET-1 21-D-NW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-ET-2 21-C-SW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-ET-3 Xochimilco West 21-D-NW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-ET-4 Xochimilco West 52-A-SE JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-LT-1 Xochimilco West 21-F-SW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-LT-2 Xochimilco West 21-F-SW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-LT-3 Xochimilco West 21-C-SW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-LT-4 Xochimilco West 21-D-NW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-LT-5 Xochimilco West 21-D-NW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-LT-6 Xochimilco West 52-D-NW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-LT-7 Xochimilco West 52-D-NW JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-LT-8 Xochimilco West 52-F-North JRP 1972 (Box 18)
      - XW-Az-1 Xochimilco West 21-E-SE JRP 1972 (Box 18)